<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <LetterLabelAnimaThrumboPasses>Anima thrumbo</LetterLabelAnimaThrumboPasses>
  <LetterAnimaThrumboPasses>This one-of-a-kind thrumbo has mutated for unknown reason. Now it is connected with anima trees and therefore received some unique attributes. The thrumbo is gentle by nature, but extremely dangerous when enraged. While its long fur is exceptionally beautiful, its hide is also incredibly resistant to damage, infused with bioluminescent micro-organisms. Its razor-sharp horn is even harder and sharper than the horn of a regular trumbo, it also fetches a huge price.\n\nLegends say that person who eats the heart of this creature will form psylink. \n\nAnima thrumbo will leave in a few days.</LetterAnimaThrumboPasses>

  <LetterLabelAnimaWargsPass>Anima wargs</LetterLabelAnimaWargsPass>
  <LetterWargsPass>These wargs have mutated for unknown reason. Now they are connected with anima trees and therefore became bigger, stronger and faster than regular wargs. \n\nMaybe if you manage to tame a couple of them, they will serve well for the defense of the settlement. \n\nTheir razorfangs could serve as good weapons.</LetterWargsPass>

  <LetterLabelAnimaBearPasses>Anima bear</LetterLabelAnimaBearPasses>
  <LetterAnimaBearPasses>This extremly rare bear has mutated for unknown reason. Now it is connected with anima trees and has its own little anima tree on its back. The anima bear is capable of using its massive strength and deadly claws to kill almost every living creature. It is quite quick for its size. \n\nLegends say that anima tree on the back of this bear spreads a psychic sooth. \n\nAnima bear will leave in a few days.</LetterAnimaBearPasses>

  <LetterLabelAnimaYaksPass>Anima yaks</LetterLabelAnimaYaksPass>
  <LetterAnimaYakPass>These yaks have mutated for unknown reason. Now they are connected with anima trees and therefore received some unique attributes. They are a bit bigger than a regular yaks and have very expensive, insulating and beautiful wool, though they give milk much less frequently. This wool can be used to make incredibly warm and luxurious clothing. \n\nLegends say that a businessman named Helixien bought an agricultural planet on which he lived only by selling anima yak wool. \n\nAnima yaks will leave in a few days.</LetterAnimaYakPass>

</LanguageData>